chinet.org 2001-12-01

# CHI: Privacy Statement

            |  **Privacy Statement for  
Cultural Homestay International**

> Cultural Homestay International has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this site. 
> 
> **Information This Site Gathers/Tracks and How We Use It**
> 
> The Cultural Homestay International Web site logs IP addresses for systems administration purposes. An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. IP addresses are logged by us to track a user's session. This gives Cultural Homestay International an idea of which parts of our site users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous, except for suspected cases of abuse or harassment. 
> 
> On certain pages, such as the Request For Further Information forms, we ask users to provide us with their names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, demographic, and other personal information. This personal information is only gathered by us with the user's knowing and active permission and participation. 
> 
> We review and discard the information in some cases, while in others we may use the information to tailor our user's Web experience, generate anonymous statistics, or to contact users via email or postal mail (e.g. to send newsletters, further information on our programs, etc.) at their request. 
> 
> **Sharing of the Information This Site Gathers/Tracks**
> 
> We do not share personally identifiable information with anybody outside of Cultural Homestay International. 
> 
> **Use of Cookies**
> 
> We use cookies on some parts of our web site to transfer data between web pages. Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies make Web surfing easier for you by saving your passwords, transactions, and preferences while you're at a web site. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them at most major Web sites. Once you leave the Cultural Homestay International Web site, all cookies sent to you by our site are deleted from your computer. We also use WebTrends Live on parts of our site to conduct anonymous web traffic analysis for our site. While WebTrends Live makes use of cookies, no personal information is ever collected or analyzed by this service. For more information on WebTrends Live, please visit their site at <http://www.webtrendslive.com/privacy_policy.htm>. 
> 
> **Privacy Policies for Individuals 16 and Under:**
> 
> No information should be submitted to or posted at Cultural Homestay International's web site by children 16 years of age or under without their parent's or guardian's consent. No information collected from children 16 years of age or under is used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside Cultural Homestay International. 
> 
> **Opt-Out Policy**
> 
> Our site provides users the opportunity to choose not to receive further communications from us by removing their information from our database through the following options: 
> 
>   * You can send email to [chimain@msn.com](mailto:chimain@msn.com)
>   * You can send mail to the following postal address:  
>  Cultural Homestay International  
>  104 Butterfield Road  
>  San Anselmo, California 94960 
>   * You can call the following telephone number: (415) 459-5397 
> 

> 
> **Correct / Update Policy**
> 
> This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 
> 
>   * You can send email to [chimain@msn.com](mailto:chimain@msn.com)
>   * You can send mail to the following postal address:  
>  Cultural Homestay International  
>  104 Butterfield Road  
>  San Anselmo, California 94960 
>   * You can call the following telephone number: (415) 459-5397 
> 

> 
> **Contacting the Web Site**
> 
> If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 
> 
> Stephen Greenstein  
>  Cultural Homestay International  
>  104 Butterfield Road  
>  San Anselmo, California 94960 
> 
> or email [stevegrn@syix.com](mailto:stevegrn@syix.com)

* * *

Return to CHI home page. If you have any problem browsing our web site, please contact [stevegrn@syix.com](mailto:stevegrn@syix.com)

Copyright © 1998, Cultural Homestay International  
This page was last modified 02/19/2020 21:24:52
